Guide to the Central Washington University Office of Alumni Relations, Memorabilia 1890s-2005
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections
- 1 Colclough china teacup and saucer set, England, circa 1948-1954; 067-06-73-242 (Box 19)
  Both pieces have the number 6594
- 1 Duchess bone china, England, 067-06-73-243 (Box 19)
  Back of plate: “Helen (Nelson) Wyatt, 1916”
- 1 Elizabethan “Caprice” footed teacup and saucer set, England, 067-06-73-244 (Box 19)
  White, hand-painted pink and yellow floral sprays, gold trim
- 1 Foley bone china footed teacup and saucer set, England, circa 1930-1936; 067-06-73-245 (Box 19)
  Back of plate: “Lura Grenia, 1923”
- 1 Foley bone china footed teacup and saucer set, England, circa 1930-1939; 067-06-73-246 (Box 19)
  Back of plate: “Marjorie Tjossem, 1933”
- 1 Foley “Windsor-Burgundy” footed teacup and saucer set, England, circa 1936-1963; 067-06-73-247 (Box 19)
  Back of plate: “Virginia Funkley Ward, 1929 Teacher Ed.”
- 1 Fred Roberts Company (San Francisco) footed teacup and saucer set, Japan, circa 1950s; 067-06-73-248 (Box 20)
  Back of plate: “Irene (Olson) Simcox, 1945.”
- 1 Gladstone bone china footed teacup and saucer set, England, circa 1952-1961; 067-06-73-249 (Box 20)
  Back of plate: “Lucille Scroup Livingston, 1931.”
- 1 Grosvenor bone china footed teacup and saucer set, England, circa 1930s; 067-06-73-250 (Box 20)
  Grosvenor was made by Jackson & Gosling (1866-1961). Back of plate: “Olive Miller, 1929.”
- 1 Haviland teacup and saucer, France, circa 1894-1931; 067-06-73-251 (Box 20)
  Back of plate: “Clair Cartledge Schluter, 1928.”
- 1 Theodore Haviland teacup and saucer set, New York, 1937-1956; 067-06-73-252 (Box 20)
  Back of plate: “Mary Hansen, 1947.”
- 1 Hermann Ohme “Old Ivory” teacup and saucer set, Silesia (now Poland), circa 1882; 067-06-73-253 (Box 20)
  The teacup has a crown, the Ohme initials, and “Silesia.” The plate has the “Old Ivory” mark, with the numbers XI and 107.
- 1 Jason bone china teacup and saucer set, England, 067-06-73-254 (Box 20)
  Back of plate: “Lydia (Guild) Strickland, 1927”
- 1 Jason bone china teacup and saucer set, England, 067-06-73-255 (Box 20)
  Back of plate: “Nada (Clark) McMurrin, 1970.”
- 1 Mikasa “Silver Maple” teacup, Narumi, Japan, 067-06-73-256 (Box 20)
  Cup may have been a match to the Kaysons’ “Golden Rhapsody” plate
- 1 Kaysons “Golden Rhapsody” saucer, Japan, 1961; 067-06-73-256 (Box 20)
  Back of plate: “Adolf (‘Swede’) Lindquist, 1928.”
- 1 Melba bone china teacup and saucer, England, 067-06-73-257 (Box 20)
  Back of plate: “Catherine (‘Kitty’) Moe, 1928 graduate with teaching certificate”
- 1 Paragon fine bone china teacup and saucer set, England, circa 1933-1938; 067-06-73-258 (Box 21)
  Back of plate: “Joyce Pugh Johnson, 1945.”
- 1 Paragon fine bone china footed eacup and saucer set, England, circa 1933-1938; 067-06-73-259 (Box 21)
  Marked with “by appointment the Queen and H.M. Queen Mary.” Saucer has hand-painted number on back (97655 Y). Cup has “Y.”
- 1 Paragon fine bone china footed teacup and saucer set, England, circa 1935; 067-06-73-260 (Box 21)
  White with green patterned border scroll and gold trim
- 1 Paragon fine bone china footed teacup and saucer set, England, circa 1957; 067-06-73-261 (Box 21)
  Light yellow with heavy gold filigree and a red rose in cup and center of plate
- 1 Paragon “Dogwood” footed teacup and saucer set, England, 067-06-73-262 (Box 21)
  Back of plate: “Olive Miller, 1929”
- 1 Plant “Tuscan China” bone china saucer, England, circa 1936-1947; 067-06-73-263 (Box 21)
  Back of plate: “Kathryn (Ives) Ryker, 3-year special diploma, 1933 and B.A. Education, 1959”
- 1 Royal Albert Crown china footed teacup, England, circa 1930; 067-06-73-263 (Box 21)
  May have been given as a match to Plant Tuscan plate
- 1 Queen Anne “Spring Melody” fine bone china teacup and saucer set, England, circa 1964; 067-06-73-264 (Box 21)
  Back of plate: “Lucille Livingston, 1931”
- 1 Queen Anne fine bone china teacup and saucer, England, circa 1980; 067-06-73-265 (Box 21)
  Back of plate: “Rebecca Thompson, CWU 1975 Speech and Drama in Secondary Education”
- 1 Queen’s bone china “Moss Rose” footed teacup and saucer set, England, circa 1952; 067-06-73-266 (Box 21)
  Part of the “Countryside Series.” Queen’s is connected to the Rosina China Co., Ltd. The cup is numbered 15; the saucer has a 3.
- 1 Radfords bone china footed teacup and saucer set, England, circa 1928-1957; 067-06-73-267 (Box 21)
  Back of plate: “Alice Brandt Kelly, 1927”
- 1 Regency bone china cup and saucer set, England, 067-06-73-268 (Box 21)
  Back of plate: “Vera Williams, 1926 & 1958”
- 1 Regency bone china footed teacup and saucer set, England, circa 1953; 067-06-73-269 (Box 21)
- 1 Rosenthal footed teacup, Germany, 067-06-73-270 (Box 22)
  White with fluting
- 1 Rosenthal Studio-linie “Porcelain-noire” saucer, Germany, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-271 (Box 22)
  Black with no detail
- 1 Roslyn “Moss Rose” footed teacup, saucer, plate set, England, circa 1950; 067-06-73-272 (Box 22)
  Back of plate: “Vera Woodall, 1936”
- 1 Rosina bone china footed teacup and saucer set, England, circa 1952; 067-06-73-273 (Box 22)
  Back of plate: “Elsie Roseburg, 1916”
- 1 Royal Adderley “Poinsettia” bone china teacup and saucer, England, circa 1962-1964; 067-06-73-274 (Box 22)
  Back of plate: “Lydia Vanderstaay (Graber)”
- 1 Royal Albert Crown china, England, circa 1904; 067-06-73-275 (Box 22)
  Back of plate: “Celia Shulz, 1919”
- 1 Royal Albert Crown china, England, circa 1904; 067-06-73-276 (Box 22)
  Back of plate: “Barbara Williams Carson, 1941-1945”
- 1 Royal Albert bone china demitasse cup and saucer, England, circa 1927-1935; 067-06-73-277 (Box 22)
  Reg. No. 769616. Hand-painted number on cup is 8237 G (or 6). Back of plate: “Lucille Nelson, 1927.”
- 1 Royal Albert Crown china cup and saucer set, England, circa 1960s; 067-06-73-278 (Box 22)
  White, hand-painted blue and purple buds, blue trim
- 1 Royal Albert Canada “From Sea to Sea” footed teacup and saucer set, England, circa 1980s-2005; 067-06-73-279 (Box 22)
  White with multicolored maple leaves and Canadian flag
- 1 Royal Albert “Symphony Series” footed teacup and saucer set, England, circa 1970s; 067-06-73-280 (Box 22)
  White with yellow band, burgundy roses, gold trim
- 1 Royal Albert “Celebration” footed teacup and saucer set, England, circa 1970s; 067-06-73-281 (Box 22)
  Back of plate: “Marcella (Braden) Dodd, 1939 Alum, Teacher Certification”
- 1 Royal Albert bone china “Marguerite” footed teacup and saucer set, England, circa 1980s; 067-06-73-282 (Box 22)
  White with blue, daisy-like flowers and gold trim. Mary R. Gruetzmann.
- 1 Royal Albert bone china “Petit Point” teacup and saucer set, England, circa 1930; 067-06-73-283 (Box 22)
  Registered No. 778676 for both cup and plate. Back of plate: “Margaret Laughlin.”
- 1 Royal Albert “Dainty Dinah” Series footed teacup and saucer set, England, circa 1935-1950s; 067-06-73-284 (Box 23)
  Numbered 2658T (cup only). Back of plate: “Grace Brandt Coldwell, 1927.”
- 1 Royal Albert footed teacup and saucer set, England, circa 1935-1950; 067-06-73-285 (Box 23)
  White background with blue pansy and green leaf chintz pattern
- 1 Royal Darwood bone china teacup and saucer set, England, circa 1980s; 067-06-73-286 (Box 23)
- 1 Royal Grafton footed teacup and saucer set, England, 067-06-73-287 (Box 23)
  White with faint, scalloped shape
- 1 Royal Grafton fine bone china footed teacup and saucer, England, circa 1957; 067-06-73-288 (Box 23)
  White with blue flowers, brown buds and burnished gold trim
- 1 Royal London bone china teacup and saucer set, England, 067-06-73-289 (Box 23)
  “D” and “x1611/86” painted on cup. Back of plate: “Lia (Lucchesi) Mori, 1945.”
- 1 Royal Albert “Laurentian Snowdrop” bone china footed teacup and saucer set, England, 067-06-73-290 (Box 23)
  Pattern number 2234. Back of plate: “Lia (Lucchesi) Mori, 1945.”
- 1 Royal Standard “Virginia Stock” teacup and saucer set, England, 067-06-73-291 (Box 23)
  White with pink stock in chintz pattern
- 1 Royal Tara “Trellis Shamrock” fine bone china footed cup and saucer set, Ireland, circa 2000; 067-06-73-292 (Box 23)
  Purchased at the Notre Dame bookstore
- 1 Royal Winton Grimwades bone china saucer, England, circa 1952; 067-06-73-293 (Box 23)
  Chintz pattern, gold, blue and pink flowers, gold trim
- 1 Saji footed demitasse cup and saucer set, Japan, 067-06-73-294 (Box 23)
  Gilded trim and flowers with gold embellishment, hand-painted
- 1 Saji fancy china footed teacup and saucer set, Occupied Japan, circa 1945-1952; 067-06-73-295 (Box 23)
  Back of plate: “Russ Wiseman, 1942 & 1955.”
- 1 Taylor and Kent “Eskimo” bone china teacup and saucer set, England, 067-06-73-296 (Box 23)
  Mark: “made for Indian Arts and Crafts.”
- 1 Tientsin porcelain coffee cup and saucer set, China, 067-06-73-297 (Box 24)
  Back of plate: “Kathryn Johannes, 1934”
- 1 Tientsin porcelain coffee cup and saucer, China, 067-06-73-298 (Box 24)
  Back of plate: “Kathryn Johannes, 1937.”
- 1 Victoria C&E bone china “Chelsea” teacup and saucer, England, 067-06-73-299 (Box 24)
  Back of plate: “Rose St. Luise Anderson, 1929.”
- 1 Victoria C&E bone china teacup and saucer set, England, circa 1930; 067-06-73-300 (Box 24)
  Wildflowers and gold trim
- 1 Waterford china “Lismore Platinum,” England, circa 2000; 067-06-73-301 (Box 24)
  White with silver gilding
- 1 Windsor bone china footed teacup and saucer set, England, circa 1950s; 067-06-73-302 (Box 24)
  Back of plate: “Jeannie (Blue) Brandt, 1991”
- 1 “Tokyo China” hand-painted, Japan, 067-06-73-303 (Box 24)
  Mark is a wreath with “C” and crown
- 1 unmarked Imari pattern? Coffee cup and saucer, Japan, 067-06-73-304 (Box 24)
  Back of plate: “Allene Wright.”
- 1 Chinese-character-marked footed teacup and saucer set, China, 067-06-73-305 (Box 24)
  Back of plate: “Allene Wright”
- 1 unmarked luster, three-footed teacup and saucer set, location unknown, 067-06-73-306 (Box 24)
  White with purple luster, cross-hatch pattern in gold with blue grapes and rust-colored leaves
- 1 unmarked footed teacup and saucer set, 067-06-73-307 (Box 24)
  Light pink with maroon flowers and heavily gilded
- 1 unmarked demitasse and saucer set, 067-06-73-308 (Box 24)
  Off-white, worn gilding and pink flower transfer
- 1 marked footed teacup and saucer, India, 067-06-73-309 (Box 24)
  Made in India for Marshall Field department store
- 1 marked teacup, saucer, and plate set, Japan or China, 067-06-73-310 (Box 25)
  Back of plate: “Dorra Cissell, 1936, Educ.”
- 1 unmarked sugar / creamer set, 067-06-73-311A-B (Box 25)
  Off-white with gilded pattern on rim edge and handle
- 1 Alfred Meakin / Jonroth “Old English StaffordshireWare” teacup and saucer set, England, circa 1909; 067-06-73-312 (Box 25)
  Jonroth was a company specializing in imports of historical or souvenir designs. The Jonroth company used other china manufacturers to produce these wares, including a long-term partnership with Adams.
- 1 Arabia earthenware cup and saucer set, Finland, 067-06-73-313 (Box 25)
  Back of plate: “Liljen (Jaskar) Gray, 1992 B.A. and 1994 M.A.”
- 1 Belleek “Shamrock” teacup and saucer, Ireland, circa 1997-1999; 067-06-73-314 (Box 25)
  Cream-colored basketweave with green shamrocks
- 1 Spode “Chinese Rose” teacup and saucer set, England, 1931; 067-06-73-315 (Box 25)
  Original pattern done c. 1815. This remake (number 2/9253) is on the Spode Imperial earthenware and there are at least 11 known versions.
- 1 Copeland Spode “India Tree” teacup and saucer set, England, circa 1867-1976; 067-06-73-316 (Box 25)
  Pattern known as “Indian Tree,” immitates a Chinese pattern from the Yung-Cheng period (1725-1735). More than 20 versions of the pattern extant. Spode produced it 1867 to 2004. Back of plate: “Dorothy Freeman Evans, Certificate 1943, B.A. Education, 1967.”
- 1 Spode (Copeland’s) Centurion “Cynthia,” England, 067-06-73-317 (Box 25)
  Back of plate: “Lillian Peckenpaugh, 1912”
- 1 marked footed teacup and saucer set, 067-06-73-318 (Box 25)
  Back of plate: “Marguerite (Albert) Kelly, 1931”
- 1 unmarked footed teacup and saucer set, location unknown, 067-06-73-319 (Box 25)
  Back of plate: “Jane and [Bird? Bond?] Brandt”
- 1 unmarked footed teacup and saucer set, Japan, 067-06-73-320 (Box 25)
  No mark but “Made in Japan.” Back of plate: “Clara (Haase) Morton, 1926.”
- 1 unmarked candle holder, Royal Hawaiian, 067-06-73-321 (Box 26)
  Pink, 5”x10”. Moroccan structure, possibly from the Royal Hawaiian hotel.
- 1 Royal Hawaiian candlestick, 067-06-73-322 (Box 26)
  Pink, 6.5”x12”, Angel
- 1 Royal Hawaiian clock, 067-06-73-323 (Box 26)
  Pink, 10.5”x15”, Rococo-styled with cherubs, battery operated
- 1 Royal Hawaiian teacup and saucer set, 067-06-73-324 (Box 26)
  Pink, plain design with “The Royal Hawaiian” logo on cup and saucer
- 1 Loch Ness monster ceramic figurine, 4 pieces, Scotland, 067-06-73-325 (Box 26)
  Approximately 12” in length
- 1 miniature figurine of Stirling Castle, Scotland, 067-06-73-326 (Box 26)
  “Hand crafted in Scotland by Impression”
- 1 handmade decorative mold plate of Barge Hall, 067-06-73-327 (Box 26)
  Bottom of plate: “State Normal School, Ellensburg, Washington” and number: 2897
- 1 Central Washington State College collector stein, circa 1950s; 067-06-73-328 (Box 27)
  Blue with gold writing of college name and seal, gold trim
- 1 CWU collector mug, Ohio, circa 1960s; 067-06-73-329 (Box 27)
  Made by the W.C. Bunting Company, East Liverpool, Ohio. Serial number: 43920.
- 1 CWU collector mug, circa 1980-2000; 067-06-73-330 (Box 27)
  White with red triangle and silver square
- 1 faux pewter / plastic stein with CWU seal, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-331 (Box 27)
  Sticky note on bottom: “Dan, here’s another goodie, Duncan Perry”
- 1 clear glass bottle with stopper lid, Millville, NJ, circa 1903-1926; 067-06-73-332 (Box 27)
  Mark on bottle: “M.B.W.” (Millville Bottle Works made chemical and laboratory bottles.)
- 1 Central Washington State College collector fluted glass, circa 1950s; 067-06-73-333 (Box 27)
  Clear glass with etching or transfer of College seal in pewter-colored trim
- 1 green glass award, circa 1950s; 067-06-73-334 (Box 27)
  Reads: “1993 Excellence in Construction—Remodeling / Renovation Over 1 Million. Barge Hall Renovation.” Award given by the Associated Builders and Constructors, Inc., Pacific NW Chapter.
- 1 Carmody Hall plate, circa 1947-1951 (Box 27)
  Back reads: “1947 to 1951. To Mrs. Crum, in appreciation, from your Boys.” Includes letter from Mrs. Mabel T. Crum (former house mother for Carmody Hall).
- 1 pewter belt buckle, “Ellensburg Rodeo”, 1991; 067-06-73-035 (Box 28)
- 1 pewter belt buckle, “Ellensburg Rodeo”, 1991; 067-06-73-336 (Box 28)
- 1 metal belt buckle in black box, 067-06-73-037 (Box 28)
- 1 metal belt buckle, 1948; 067-06-73-038 (Box 28)
- 1 WSNS sweater pin, circa 1930s; 067-06-73-335 (Box 28)
- 2 Kappa Delta Pi pins, circa 1940s (Box 28)
- 1 group of CWCE gold jewelry, circa 1950s; 067-06-73-336 (Box 28)
- 1 gold medallion, 067-06-73-337 (Box 28)
- 4 plastic Centennial commemorative “chips”, 1991; 067-06-73-338 (Box 28)
- 3 enamel CWU Centennial lapel pins, 1991; 067-06-73-339 (Box 28)
- 3 plastic CWU alumni lapel pins, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-340 (Box 28)
- 2 enamel Wildcat head lapel pins, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-341 (Box 28)
- 2 metal / enamel collectible spoons, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-342 (Box 28)
- 1 metal alumni key chain, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-343 (Box 28)
- Assorted buttons, circa 2000s; 067-06-73-344 (Box 28)
- 3 plastic hand-clappers, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-345 (Box 28)
- 1 “Musical Key Tag”, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-346 (Box 28)
- 3 musical buttons, 1989; 067-06-73-347 (Box 28)
- 2 window decals, circa 1980s-1990s; 067-06-73-348 (Box 28)
- 2 CWU alumni calendar planners, 2000; 067-06-73-349 (Box 28)
- 1 WSNS “Scribulus Club” shirt pin, 1924; 067-06-73-350 (Box 28)
- 6 CWSC basketball presentation awards, 1974 (Box 29)
- Swimming buttons (Box 29)
- 1 commemorative basketball in display case, 1998-1999 (Box 30)
  Display case reads: “Pacific West Conference, Men’s Regional Champions, 1998-1999.” Basketball was signed by team.
- 1 commemorative basketball in display case, 1999-2000 (Box 31)
  Display case reads: “Pacific West Conference NCAA Division II, Men’s Basketball 21-7, 1999-2000.” Basketball was signed by team.
- 1 commemorative basketball in display case, 1999-2000 (Box 32)
  Display case reads: “Pacific West Conference, NCAA Division II, Women’s Basketball 19-8, 1999-2000.” Basketball was signed by team.
- 1 commemorative basketball in display case, 2000; 067-06-73-085 (Box 33)
  Basketball reads: “100 Victories. Nov. 17, 2000. Greg Sparling, ’95-’01. CWU 74, VA Union 69.” Basketball was signed by team.
- Field hockey stick, circa 1970s; 067-06-73-045 (Box 34)
- Field hockey stick, circa 1970s; 067-06-73-046 (Box 34)
- Field hockey stick, circa 1970s; 067-06-73-047 (Box 34)
- Marching band hat, circa 1940s; 067-06-73-153 (Box 35)
  Branded “De Moulin Bros., Greenville, Ill.” Marked with “CWC” metallic details.
- Marching band hat, circa 1940s; 067-06-73-154 (Box 35)
- Marching band hat, circa 1940s; 067-06-73-155 (Box 35)
- 1 black marching band jacket, 067-06-73-156 (Box 35)
  Tagged “1034”
- Commemorative ribbon, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-157 (Box 36)
- Commemorative ribbon, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-158 (Box 36)
- Commemorative ribbon, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-159 (Box 36)
- Commemorative ribbon, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-160 (Box 36)
- Commemorative ribbon, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-161 (Box 36)
- Commemorative ribbon, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-162 (Box 36)
- Commemorative ribbon, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-163 (Box 36)
- Commemorative ribbon, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-164 (Box 36)
- Commemorative ribbon, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-165 (Box 36)
- Commemorative ribbon, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-166 (Box 36)
- Commemorative ribbon, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-167 (Box 36)
- Commemorative ribbon, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-168 (Box 36)
- Commemorative ribbon, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-169 (Box 36)
- Commemorative ribbon, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-170 (Box 36)
- Commemorative ribbon, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-171 (Box 36)
- Commemorative ribbon, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-172 (Box 36)
- Commemorative ribbon, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-173 (Box 36)
- Commemorative ribbon, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-174 (Box 36)
- Commemorative ribbon, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-175 (Box 36)
- Commemorative ribbon, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-176 (Box 36)
- Commemorative ribbon, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-177 (Box 36)
- Commemorative ribbon, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-178 (Box 36)
- Commemorative ribbon, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-179 (Box 36)
- Commemorative ribbon, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-180 (Box 36)
- Commemorative ribbon, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-181 (Box 36)
- Commemorative ribbon, circa 1990s; 067-06-73-182 (Box 36)
- 1 white “Go Wildcats” Central Washington University flag, 067-06-73-183 (Box 37)
- 1 Central Washington University Wildcats towel, 067-06-73-184 (Box 37)
- 1 Central Washington University Wildcats towel, 067-06-73-185 (Box 37)
- Football pants, 067-06-73-186 (Box 37)
- Football pants, 067-06-73-187 (Box 37)
- Football pants, 1997; 067-06-73-188 (Box 37)
- Sport coats and Letterman sweaters, circa 1930s; 067-06-73-189 (Box 38)
- Sport coats and Letterman sweaters, circa 1930s; 067-06-73-190 (Box 38)
- Sport coats and Letterman sweaters, circa 1930s; 067-06-73-191 (Box 38)
- Sport coats and Letterman sweaters, circa 1930s; 067-06-73-192 (Box 38)
- Sport coats and Letterman sweaters, circa 1930s; 067-06-73-193 (Box 38)
- Sport coats and Letterman sweaters, circa 1930s; 067-06-73-194 (Box 38)
- CWU football jersey, circa 1930s; 067-06-73-196 (Box 39)
  Burgundy, white, and blue jerseys. Two signed by Dan Murphy.
- CWU football jersey, circa 1930s; 067-06-73-197 (Box 39)
- CWU football jersey, circa 1930s; 067-06-73-198 (Box 39)
- CWU football jersey, circa 1930s; 067-06-73-199 (Box 39)
- CWU football jersey, circa 1930s; 067-06-73-200 (Box 39)
- CWU football jersey, circa 1930s; 067-06-73-201 (Box 39)
- CWU football jersey, circa 1930s; 067-06-73-202 (Box 39)
- CWU football jersey, circa 1930s; 067-06-73-203 (Box 39)
- CWU football jersey, circa 1930s; 067-06-73-204 (Box 39)
- CWU football jersey, circa 1930s; 067-06-73-205 (Box 39)
- 1 Seattle Seahawks jersey, circa 1997-2000; 067-06-73-206 (Box 40)
  Jersey for Jon Kitna, #7
- 1 Seattle Seahawks jersey, circa 1997-2000; 067-06-73-207 (Box 40)
- 1 black Cincinnati Bengals jersey, circa 2001-2006; 067-06-73-208 (Box 40)
  Jersey for Jon Kitna, #3
- 1 white San Francisco Giants jersey, circa 1970s; 067-06-73-209 (Box 40)
  Jersey for Dave North, #60. Signed by Dave Heaverlo.
- 1 white San Francisco Giants jersey, circa 1970s; 067-06-73-210 (Box 40)
- 1 white Oakland Athletics jersey, circa 1970s; 067-06-73-211 (Box 40)
  Jersey for Billy North, #4. Green and yellow text.
- 1 Central Washington University Wildcats basketball jersey, 067-06-73-212 (Box 41)
- 1 Central Washington University Wildcats basketball jersey, 067-06-73-213 (Box 41)
- 1 Central Washington University Wildcats basketball jersey, 067-06-73-214 (Box 41)
- 1 Central Washington University Wildcats basketball jersey, 067-06-73-215 (Box 41)
- 1 Central Washington University Wildcats basketball jersey, 067-06-73-216 (Box 41)
- 1 Central Washington University Wildcats basketball jersey, 067-06-73-217 (Box 41)
- 1 Central Washington University Wildcats basketball jersey, 067-06-73-218 (Box 41)
- Central Washington University Wildcats basketball shorts, 067-06-73-219 (Box 41)
- Central Washington University Wildcats basketball shorts, 067-06-73-220 (Box 41)
- Central Washington University Wildcats basketball shorts, 067-06-73-221 (Box 41)
- Central Washington University Wildcats basketball shorts, 067-06-73-222 (Box 41)
- Central Washington University Wildcats basketball shorts, 067-06-73-223 (Box 41)
- Central Washington University Wildcats basketball shorts, 067-06-73-224 (Box 41)
- Central Washington University Wildcats basketball shorts, 067-06-73-225 (Box 41)
- Calendar, Music Education Building Program, CWU news, 1983-2005 (Box-folder 42-1)
- Frank Borman (note), 1968 (Box-folder 42-2)
- Garth Brooks (note), 1999 (Box-folder 42-3)
- 50th Anniversary Biography Yearbook, 2003 (Box-folder 42-4)
- Alumni and Student Brochures,including reproduction catalog from 1952-53, 1952-2002 (Box-folder 42-5)
- School Guide, 1991-2000 (Box-folder 42-6)
- Expo Jazz Festival (Box-folder 42-7)
- Alumni Pen and Pencil (Box-folder 42-8)
- CWU Alumni clothing: 8 Alumni Shirts, 1 CWU visor, 1 green sweatshirt from 1946, 1946-1999; 067-2018 (Box 43)